Natalie Babbitt Papers 1994.0001
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Published Books, undated, 1906-
  - Jack Plank Tells Tales, 2007
    - Jacket and cover samples, undated (Box 30:, Folder 236)
    - Advance reader's copy, 2007 (Box 30:, Folder 237)
    - Publicity and reviews, 2007 (Box 30:, Folder 238)
- Series II: Published Articles and Short Stories
  - "The Good King", Redbook, 1971 (Box 25:, Folder 190)
  - "Princess and the Ogre", Children's Digest, 1977
    - Original artwork, undated (Box 25:, Folder 191)
  - "Children's Fiction", Encyclopedia Britannica, circa 1978 (Box 25:, Folder 192)
- Series III: Unpublished materials, circa 1953, circa 1963
  - "Raspberry Jones", circa 1953
    - Dummy (Box 14:, Folder 238)
  - "Alice", circa 1963
    - Original drawings (Box 14:, Folder 239)
    - Original sketches (Box 14:, Folder 240)
- Series IV: Subject Files, undated, 1953-1991
  - Articles about Natalie Babbitt, 1979-1990 (Box 26:, Folder 193)
  - Awards-- Hans C. Andersen, 1982 (Box 26:, Folder 194)
  - Camelot book covers, undated (Box 26:, Folder 195)
  - "The Cat and the Dragon's Garden", undated (Box 26:, Folder 196)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1953, 1969-1976 (Box 26:, Folder 197)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1988 (Box 26:, Folder 198)
  - Dead Man's Log, undated (Box 26:, Folder 199)
  - Interview, bibliography, undated (Box 26:, Folder 200)
  - Photographs (Box 28:, Folder 201)
  - Programs, undated, 1979-1986 (Box 26:, Folder 202)
  - Publicity and reviews, undated, 1974-1986 (Box 26:, Folder 203)
  - Publisher's catalogs, 1968-1984 (Box 27:, Folder 204)
  - Reviews by Natalie Babbitt, undated, 1971-1991 (Box 27:, Folder 205)
  - Reviews--General, 1976-1990 (Box 27:, Folder 206)
  - Ribbon, 1981 (Box 27:, Folder 207)
- Series V: Artifacts, undated
  - Pirate flag (Box 32)
  - "Nellie" model (Box 32)
  - Straw hat with ribbon (Box 32)
  - Crab and anchor models (Box 32)
- 2013.0076 Addition, 2013.0076
  - Box 1: Moon Over High Street, Tuck Everlasting Correspondence, undated, 1981-82, 1992, 1999, 2012 (Box 1)
    Scope and Content Note
    [Subjects include: galley proofs of Babbitt novels "Barking With the Big Dogs," "Moon Over High Street," "Eyes of the Amaryllis," and various screenplays of film "Tuck Everlasting." Also included is correspondence between Babbitt and various publishers dealing with the corrections and output of Moon over High Street, film of Tuck Everlasting, and with Amaryllis Publishing company. Lots of negative photographs & stills from Tuck Everlasting filming. Financial records dealing with the budget of Amaryllis, Babbitt's royalties from Disney, HBO, etc. for the Tuck Everlasting film, along with the distribution of the film and various checks, scans of checks and receipts dealing with the distributionof the book & film. Also included is ephemera, such as loose book covers for "Moon Over High Street," the program for a musical version of "Tuck Everlasting," a bookfair catalog & other ads dealing with Babbitt's books. Also included are newspapers reviewing and featuring the film adaptation of "Tuck Everlasting."]
  - Box 2: Galley Proofs of Various Novels (Box 2)
    [Subjects include: Correspondence, dummies and galley proofs of "Peacock & other Poems," dummies of "Top of the Pool," "All the Secrets of Life," "While the Zoo Keeper Slept," "The Lion's Share," "Grome, "Barking With the Big Dogs," and "Moon Over High Street." Also publications, showcasing "Jack Plank Tells Stories" in Top 100 kids books of 2007, the century."